Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Organizations
  - Subseries A: National Academies
    - Workshop on Philosophy and Engineering, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - William A. Wulf, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Wulf / Vest / Davis, 2007 June (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - National Academy of Engineering of Korea, 2005 July-August (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - National Research Council – Governing Board, 2003 June (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - N.R.C. Committee on Global Science and Technology Strategies and Their Effect on U.S. National Security, 2009 September (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Council – N.R.C. Governing Board, 2009 February (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - N.R.C. – Governing Board, 2008 October-November (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Division on Engineering and Physical Sciences – Board on Infrastructure and Constructed Environment, 2008 November-December (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - The Bridge – Editorials, 1997-2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Dr. Ralph J. Cicerone, 2004 June (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Secretary – Correspondence, 2004 January-March (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Harvey Ludwig Reference, 2005 January-August (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - National Associate, 2001 December (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Foreign Secretary – Miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Foreign Secretary Reports, 2005 February (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Foreign Secretary Reports, 2003 September, 2004 July (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering Visit, 2005 April-June (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering Visit, 2005 June-December (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Foreign Secretary Job Description, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Regional Meeting – Boston, MA, 2005 May (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous, 2005 September-October (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering, 2004 January-April (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering – Trips, 2005 March-August (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering – William A. Wulf, 2005 May-October (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering – Miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - National Academy of Engineering – Foreign Academies, 2010 August-November (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting, 2010 October (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Foreign Secretary – Second Candidacy, 2006 August, 2007 April (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - N.A.S. – Computer Science and Telecommunications Board – Reviews – RESTRICT, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Interacademy Programs Between the United States and Eastern Europe, 2009 April (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - The Bridge – Editorials, 1997-2009 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – Colloquium Proceedings, 1995 March 24 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Chinese Academy of Engineering, 2007 October (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - International Council of Academies of Engineering and Technological Sciences – International Symposium, 2008 June 26 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - German-American Frontiers of Engineering Symposium – Potsdam, Germany, 2009 April 22-25 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - U.S-Indian Symposium on Food Processing Technologies for Food Safety and Innovation, 2010 February 25-26 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Jennifer Weeks, 2009 January 15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - N.R.C. – Landmines, 2000 March-August (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - N.R.C. – Landmines, 2000 September-2001 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment, 1995 January-1996 December (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Board on African Science Academy Development – The Annual Bias and Conflict of Interest Discussion for the Board, 2010 November 23 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Office of International Affairs – National Research Council – Prospectus for National Knowledge Assessment, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Alternative Technologies to Replace Anti-Personnel Landmines, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - National Research Council – "Making the Nation Safe from Fire: A Path Forward in Research", 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - National Research Council – "Making the Nation Safer: The Role of Science and Technology in Countering Terrorism", 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - National Research Council – "Making the Nation Safer: The Role of Science and Technology in Countering Terrorism" – Prepublication Copy, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Sam Florman – Correspondence, 2004 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "Foreign Secretary Column" – The Bridge, 2003 July 30 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Adriano De Mario – Correspondence, 1994 February 27 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - United States-Mexico Foundation for Science, 2004 April – 2005 November, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Dr. Herbert Gleiter – Leopoldina Academy, 2007 June- August (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - New York Times – Landmines, 2001 March 22 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Interacademy Panel on International Issues – Workshop on Habitat II, 1996 January 22-24 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - National Academies Roundtable on Science and Technology for Sustainability, 2004 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Russian Academy of Sciences, 2004 August-September (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Meeting on "Building Iraqi Capacity – Cooperation for the Restoration of the Mesopotamian Marshlands – Washington, DC, 2004 April 15 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Foreign Associates, 2003 June - 2004 Febraury (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - French-U.S. Relations, 2004 January 5 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Foreign Secretary Correspondence, 2003 November, 2004 April (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Secretary Appointment Letter, 2002 December - 2003 June (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Landmines Committee, 2006 January-February (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Foreign Secretary – Miscellaneous, 2004 November - 2006 January (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Science Education K-12, 1996 April - 1997 August (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Committee on Science Education K-12, 1997 October-November, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment, 1994 August - 1995 March (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Dennis Chamot, 1994 October (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Iran, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Iran, 2006 January-June (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Iran, 2006 June - September (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – Washington, DC, 1997 March 14-15 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – Washington, DC, 1995 March 23-25 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – Miscellaneous, 1995 April - 1997 April (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - William A. Wulf, 2005 June 7 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - USAID, 2005 March 24 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Seminar on "Building and Sustaining Capacity in Science, Technology and Health in Developing Countries" - Washington, DC, 2003 November 5-6 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - National Research Council – Land Mines Committee, 1999 September-December (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - National Research Council – Land Mines Committee, 2000 January-March (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - National Research Council – Land Mines Committee, 2000 March-June (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council – Land Mines Committee, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Workshop on "Engineering, Social Justice, and Sustainable Community Development", 2008 October 2-3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Board on Engineering Education – CETS/OSEP, 1991 April 25-26 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Urban Sustainability – Correspondence, 2004 June 10 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Presidents' Circle of the National Academies, 2005 November 6-8 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The National Academies – Bruce Alberts, 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Liaisons, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Council of Academies of Engineering and Technological Sciences, 2006 April – May (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Project on Large Urban Areas ("Megacities") – Steering Committee Meeting, 2000 May 9 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - German American Frontiers of Engineering Symposium, 2009 April (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Joe Jacob's – N.A.E. Nomination, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Secretary – Miscellaneous, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - N.R.C. – Governing Board, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Proposal for Cooperation with Moslem World, 2009 October (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - National Academy of Engineering of Korea, 2009 October (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Indo-U.S. Science and Technology Forum, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Council of Academies of Engineering and Technological Sciences, 2010 June (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - European Frontiers of Engineering Program, 2008 October (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Herbert Gleiter – Joint Conference – Karlsruhe Institute of Technology, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - The Bridge – Correspondence, 2005 April-May (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Interacademy Workshop on Science and Technology and the Future Development of Societies – Iran, 2006 February (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - National Academy of Sciences – Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment, 1994 October 20-21 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - N.R.C. – Board on Engineering Education, 1994 September-October (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - N.R.C. – Board on Engineering Education, 1994 November (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - N.R.C. – The Hydrogen Economy, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - N.R.C. – Joint Task Force on Engineering Education, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - N.R.C. – National Science Education Standards: An Enhanced Sampler, 1993 February (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - N.R.C. – Dr. Michael Greene – "Knowledge Assessment in Prince Edward Island" – Draft, 1998 March 20 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Board on Infrastructure and the Constructed Environment – "Financing Tomorrow's Infrastructure", 1995 October 20 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Prospectus for National Knowledge Assessment, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Council Meeting / N.R.C. Governing Board – Irvine, CA, 2011 February (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - U.S. Metropolitan Development Trends, 1994 November (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Counterterrorism Challenges for Russia and the United States, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - The Royal Academy of Engineering – DVD, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Introductory Mailing, 2011 January (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Bridge – Carol Arenberg, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Foreign Secretary, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - The Bridge – Maxine Savitz, 2009 February-June (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Foreign Secretary – Miscellaneous, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - The Experiences and Challenges of Science and Ethics: Proceedings of an American-Iranian Workshop, 2003 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - N.R.C. - Board on Engineering Education - Washington, DC - 1, 1991 August 22-23 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - N.R.C. - Board on Engineering Education - Washington, DC - 2, 1991 August 22-23 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - The Bridge – Miscellaneous, 2009 May - 2010 March (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - The Bridge – Miscellaneous, 2010 April-May (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Bridge – Miscellaneous, 2010 June-August (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Korea – Intellectual Property Symposium, 2010 June 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Korea – Managing University Intellectual Property, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Engineering, Social Justice and Sustainable Community Development workshop – Proctor Reid, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Robert Sproull – N.R.C. Review, 2010 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Engineering and Environmental Challenges: A Technical Symposium on Earth Systems Engineering – "Rethinking Urbanization", 2000 October 24 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - National Research Council – Science and Technology for Army Homeland Security – Report 1, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - National Research Council - Science and Technology for Army Homeland Security – Report 2, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - National Research Council - Alternative Technologies to Replace Antipersonnel Landmines, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - N.A.E. - The Presidents' Circle – Speech, "Rethinking Urbanization", 2003 June 5-7 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - N.R.C. - Committee on Science Education K-12, 1998 November 24 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - N.S.F. – Final Report Based on the Workshop on Integrated Research for Civil Infrastructure, 1996 July 15-17 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - N.S.F. Grant – "The Impact of the University on Its Environment", 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Subseries B: NATO
    - Lithium Batteries Project, 1998 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Steering Group Meeting – Turkey – December 1-3, 1997, 1997 October (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Science for Peace, 1997 August - 1998 June (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Science for Stability Steering Group Visit – Lisbon, Portugal – April 15-20, 1996, 1985, 1996 January-June (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Jean-Marie Cadiou, 1995 March 20 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Science for Stability Program – Steering Committee Meeting, Greece, April 14-19, 1997, 1997 March-April (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 September-2000 October (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, April 15-17, 1999, 1999 March-August (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, September 23-25, 1999, 1999 August-September (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, January 29-31, 1998, 1998 January-February (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, 1997 May 22-24 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, November 11-14, 1998, 1998 October (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting, 1999 March-April (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - National Association for Science, Technology, and Society – Honorary Member Award, 1995 February-March (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, September 3-5, 1998, 1998 July-September (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, April 2-4, 1998, 1998 March-April (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Science for Peace Steering Group Meeting – Brussels, February 23-25, 1998, 1998 February (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Science for Peace – Miscellaneous, 1997-1998, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Science for Stability Steering Group Visit – Portugal, September 15-18, 1997, 1996 May-1997 September (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1998 September 9 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Subseries C: Project 2061
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Panel, 1988 January 15 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Final Report, 1988 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - D.C. Staff – Panel Chairs – Correspondence, 1985 October - 1987 May (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Dr. Samuel Devons – Nevis Laboratories, Columbia University, 1985 November - 1986 July (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Paul R. Garabedan – Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, NYU, 1985 November - 1986 July (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Alan H. Strahler – Hunter College, CUNY, 1985 November - 1986 June (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Dr. Spencer Weart- American Institute of Physics, 1985 November-1986 June (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - James J. Conti – Vice President for Educational Development, Polytechnic Institute of New York, Farmingdale, 1986 February-July (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Dr. Kathleen Crane – Associate Professor of Geology – Hunter College, CUNY, 1985 December - 1986 July (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - William H. Starnes, Jr. – Head, Department of Chemistry, Polytechnic University, 1986 June-July (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - John Truxal – Center for Technology and Society, SUNY at Stony Brook, 1985 December - 1986 February (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Dr. Davig M. Mog – National Research Council, 1985 December - 1986 April (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Dr. Marvin Epstein, 1986 July 31 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - David G. Copp – Bell Communications Research, 1985 November - 1986 June (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Membership Panel – Appointment Letters, 1985 October-December (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Meeting, May 14, 1986 – Panel Reports, 1986 April-May (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Meeting, April 10, 1986 – Minutes, 1986 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Panel Chairs Meeting, San Francisco, CA, March 9, 1986, 1986 February-March (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Meeting – February 24, 1986, 1986 January-March (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel, January 20, 1986, 1985 December - 1986 January (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel – December 11, 1985, 1985 November – 1986 January (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel – November 14, 1985, 1985 November (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Mathematics Panel, First Meeting – October 5, 1985, 1985 October (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel – January 13, 1986, 1986 January-March (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Published Reports, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - National Forum for School Science – Arlington, VA, 1986 November 14-15 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel Meeting, 1986 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Physical Sciences and Engineering Panel Meeting, 1986 August 7 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic University – Ad Hoc Board Committee, 1984 January - 1986 June (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic University – Ad Hoc Committee, 1986 January 16 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Expenses, 1985 December - 1986 July (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Expenses, 1986 August - 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Expenses Summary Reports, 1986 March - 1988 May (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Description of Project, 1985 October 16 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Physical Science and Engineering Panel, 1986 January-July (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Mathematics Panel, 1987 April, 1988 March (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Biology & Medicine Panel, 1985 November - 1987 May (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Technology Panel, 1985 August - 1986 November (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - "Basic Concepts in the Social and Behavioral Sciences", 1987 January, May (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Chemistry Panel, 1986 May (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Subpanel on Earth, Planetary and Astronomical Sciences, 1985 November - 1986 June (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Oceanography & Meteorology Panel, 1986 August (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Subpanel on Physics and Mathematics, 1986 April (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Information Science Sub-Panel, 1986 March-July (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Macro-Engineering Conference, 1986 March 13-14 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Meeting on July 29th at the American Institute of Physics, 1986 July 29 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Meeting – Aspen, Colorado, 1986 June 10-12 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - 2061 Today, 1996-1997, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Final Report, 1988 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "Physical and Information Sciences and Engineering", 1989 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Subseries D: Sigma Xi
    - James F. Baur, 2007 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Bugliarello Prize, 2010 November (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Forum – Correspondence, 2000 April (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - "Ethics, Values and the Promise of Science" Forum, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Lecturers, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Lecture – Bonnie Shulman, Bates College, 1996 March-October (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Lecture – Augustine J. Frederich, University of Southern Indiana, 1997 January (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Lecture – Lehigh University, 1997 February-April (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Lecture – Tidewater Virginia Chapter, 1997 February-March (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Lecture – Cerro Coso Community College, 1997 February-March (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Lecture – University of Carolina at Charlotte, 1994 October - 1997 May (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Lecture – Iowa State University of Science & Technology, 1996 November - 1997 December (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Lecture – South Dakota School of Mines and Technology, 1996 February - 1997 February (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Lecture – Christopher Newport University, 1997 October (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Lecture – University of New Mexico, 1997 September-October (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Lecture – SUNY Purchase, 1996 September-October (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Lecture – Penn State, 1996 - 1997 March (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Norman J. Field Lecture, 1996 March-October (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Lecture – East Stroudsburg, PA, 1996 October - 1997 May (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - The Greenwall Foundation Announcement, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - George Bugliarello Prize, 2000-2006 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - 2010 Bugliarello Prize (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - 1995 Sigma Xi Forum – Vannevar Bush II, Airlie Center Planning Conference, 1994 September 8-11 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Bugliarello Prize, 2007 August (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Lectures, 1997 September-October (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 2010 February (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Ethics Summit Follow Up – Correspondence, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-1997 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Executive Director Search Committee – RESTRICT, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Subseries E: Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Knowledge Parks Study
    - Association of University Research Parks AURP – Eco Development Article – "Using Technology to Enhance the Economic Efficiency of Small Retail Establishments", 2007 January – June (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Bodegas, Summer 2007, 2005-2007 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Lehman College, 2001 September (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Progress Reports, 2001 July, 2002 February (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Pause York Project, 2001 November-December (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - David Freed – CUNY, 2001 August-December (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Robert Meeder (Pittsburgh Gateways Corp), Jack Rainey (LaGuardia Community College CUNY), 2001 May (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - "Jamaica Center: A Model of Knowledge-Driven Urban Development," George Bugliarello, 2002 January 4 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation – New AirTrain Terminal Celebration, 2004 January 14 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation – Memoranda, Journal advertisement, 2002 May-September, 2004 January-February (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - "Enhancement of Economic and Social Development in New York: Two Knowledge Park Prospects" – Proposal, October 13, 2000, 2000 September-December (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Agendas, 2002 January - 2003 January (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Approved Grant Proposal, 2000 December - 2001 March (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Alfred Eisenpreis Consulting Agreement, 2001 February, May (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Congresswoman Nydia Velazquez, 2006 July-October (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Letterhead, 2001 July (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Ted Greenwood, 2001 March, October, 2005 February (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Sara Nerlove – NSF, 2006 August - 2008 October (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - York Aviation Conference, March 31, 2003, 2002 November - 2003 February (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - York College Foundation, 2004 July, September (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Jerry Posman – COO, York College, 2001 May - 2005 December (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - York College, 2001 October - 2006 January (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Jamaica Concurrent Commitment Symposium – Planning, 2002 February-March (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Request for Grant Extension, 2002 December - 2003 October (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - William B. Shore – Consulting, 1999 December - 2004 August (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Project Reports, 2002 February, 2004 October (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Craig Jenks – Airline/Aircraft Projects, 2002 April - 2004 June (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Industrial & Technology Assistance Corporation, Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 2002 April - 2003 February (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Anthony Perl - York College - Aviation Institute Inaugural Conference, 2003 March-April (Box 12, Folder 19)